let CremeBruleeQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for Regular size Ube Latte Creme Brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for Regular size Mango Jam Creme Brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for Large size Tiger Latte Creme Brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
      
    {
        "question": "What should we tell customer if they want almond milk in their creme brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the sugar options for Tiger Sugar Creme Brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Can customer make the Creme Brulee drink with no ice?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Do we offer Creme Brulee in hot?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Can customer subtitute the milk for the Creme Brulee drinks?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is best to describe what is Ube Latte Creme Brulee to the customer?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for Large size Ube Latte Creme Brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for Regular size Tiger Latte Creme Brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the recipe for Large size Mango Jam Creme Brulee?",
        "option1": "",
        "option2": "",
        "option3": "",
        "option4": "",
        "answer": 3
    }
];